Flesh and sin die.
Die with Christ, that's it.
Rise with Christ.
That's it. Holy Spirit, come.
Holy Spirit come, set her free.
Die with Christ.
Holy Spirit, more.
Come with your Holy Spirit.
Fill me up.
Just words started coming.
Thank you, Lord!
What was I doing?
- What?
What you were doing?
You were praying in tongues.
Does it hurt?
- No.
Not at all?
In Jesus' name,
I thank you. Amen.
It's done!
Hallelujah!
...over one month
and she is in shock.
It's Jesus.
I used to watch
these things on TV
and sometimes I do not believe,
but today I do believe
because it happens to me.
Pain, go now.
And you can do this.
Now get all up.
It's good, yeah?
- Yeah.
Thank you Father. Amen.
Try to feel it.
Can you feel any difference?
Seriously, it does not hurt anymore.
Wow!
God, I thank you for healing. Thank you,
the pain is going to go.
Try to feel the head.
No!
I don't feel no pain, bro.
Now the pain is gone.
Now the pain is gone, yes.
We, as the church today, are standing
in front of a new reformation.
A reformation,
where we are coming back
to what we read
in the Book of Acts.
If you look at the church today,
it is so different from what we read
in the Book of Acts.
Because we have like
2000 years of history,
where the church has been changed
again and again.
We can see that the church
in the Book of Acts was a living body.
It was a body of believers
who were led by the Holy Spirit.
The church was a movement,
a disciples' movement.
Christianity moved to Greece
and became a philosophy.
It came to Italy and
became an institution.
It came to Europe and
became a culture.
It came to America and
became a business.
If you take a body and make
a business out of a body
is that not prostitution?
And this is what we have done
today with the church.
We have prostituted the church
of Christ, the body of Christ.
Because of that, we need
to see a reformation,
where we go so much deeper.
Where we are talking about the doctrine,
we are talking about the Spirit,
and we are also talking about the whole
system, the church system.
Why we do church the way we do it.
It's time to go back to what
we read in the Book of Acts.
God is now bringing us
back to the beginning.
What a mighty God we serve.
Angels bow down.
Heaven and earth adore Him.
What a mighty God we serve.
Angels bow down.
Heaven and earth adore Him.
What makes the Book of Acts
the most unique book of the Bible,
is that the Book of Acts is
the only book in the entire Bible
and all of Scripture,
that shows us
how to actually go out
and make disciples.
If you read the gospels that
lead up to the Book of Acts,
what's interesting is,
that even though these books
were written at a time,
like when they were written,
probably about thirty years
after the cross,
but the time periods covered
are all before the cross.
So we don't see the fullness
of the Christian life there
because Christ hadn't yet died,
he hadn't yet been buried
and resurrected and sent
his Spirit.
So we don't see in the gospels
how they went out
and actually made disciples.
The Holy Spirit had
not yet been given
and plus, we didn't have
the power yet
to go out
and be successful doing this.
And I think that contributes to a lot
of the fear today
for those who don't
know the Holy Spirit.
Because Jesus told them
to go and wait.
He says, "When my Spirit comes,
you will receive power
and then you will be my witnesses."
It's real!
It's really real!
Amen, it's real!
Hallelujah.
- She just got healed.
Amazing, Jesus.
- Thank you, Jesus.
Look at that, she's walking.
I know in many churches
there is a sign
on the church wall where it's written,
'Jesus is the same yesterday,
today and forever.'
We, today as believers,
believe that
Jesus is the same
yesterday, today and forever.
But if He's the same,
the Holy Spirit is also the same.
And if the Holy Spirit is the same,
what we read in the Book of Acts
should also be the same.
By the power of Jesus Christ, she
gets healed right now.
This man has just healed this lady.
And he's overwhelmed.
It's done.
- It's done. It is finished.
It is finished, with his cry.
I was walking like this
because I could not move any faster.
What can you do now?
Sister, do like this.
I could not do this.
This I could not do.
And this I could not do.
I would've screamed up the
whole place doing that.
All glory be to His name.
In the Book of Acts we see the
very early Christians,
the very early
disciples of Christ.
They were living this
lifestyle of discipleship.
They were reaching people
in their homes, on the streets.
They met people
where they were at.
And the gospel was exploding
and spreading to the entire world.
Thousands and thousands
and thousands of people
came to faith in Jesus Christ
and were baptized
and received the Holy Spirit.
But at one point in church history,
we see that
Christianity was institutionalized and
soon became a state religion.
This hierarchy & institutionalized church
was following us through the reformation
where Luther, Calvin
and Zwingli came.
They were trying to reform and bring
us back to the real gospel,
back to the Book of Acts.
But they failed.
We still have the building.
We still have the special priesthood.
We still have people meeting
in special buildings,
on special dates, with a hierarchy
and people trying
to bring offerings to the church
to gain the favor of God.
Luther did not succeed in bringing
the church back
to what we read in the Book of Acts.
The Bible is the book of life.
And it doesn't become
the book of life by studying it.
It becomes the book of life
by living it.
I command the pain in this hand
to go, in Jesus' name.
Try to do it again.
It's gone.
What's this?
In Jesus' name,
right now. Amen.
Check it.
It's gone.
Amen.
Go, right now, in the name of Jesus.
Try again.
Bones, I command you to mend
right now in Jesus' name.
Try it out.
Is it similar to Reiki?
- No, Jesus.
Jesus, not Reiki.
- No, no. No energy?
God. No, it's not energy.
Thank you, Jesus.
What do you think about
what just happened?
It's cool.
- It's pretty cool?
We are born, put here on earth
with a purpose.
That is, to seek and find God.
The problem is that we
don't seek Him.
Because we don't seek Him,
we don't find Him.
Have you heard about Jesus?
We live 2015 years
after Jesus Christ.
God is real and He called us
to be His disciples,
Jesus' disciples, to go out
and show the world He is real.
Fifth of April, 1995, I repented.
I recognized I have sinned
and gave my life to Jesus
and a light came into my body and
I fell to the floor, and I met God.
When you become a born-again Christian,
the Spirit of God comes and lives in you
and you get to do the things Jesus did.
The Bible says that we should be
doers of the Word
and not only hearers.
If we only hear the Word and do not
do it, we are deceiving ourselves.
We are like a man
looking in a mirror
but as soon as we go away,
we have forgotten what we saw.
Sunday after Sunday there are
millions of Christians
who are sitting in church and
listening to the Word of God.
But as soon as they go away,
they have forgotten what they heard.
As a pastor,
in the last couple of years
I started to get really hungry.
I would read through the Book of Acts
and I became angry at the way
that I saw things happening
in the Book of Acts, and I didn't
see this happening
in my church, or in my own life,
or with the eldership,
or the structure of the church at all.
We weren't just going out
& healing people.
We would lay hands on people
and tell them to go home
and they'll get better maybe,
in the future, or maybe not.
But what I read in the Book of Acts
is that the Apostles
were going out and they
were just doing this stuff daily.
I really felt that
that's what I wanted.
So for two years I've been
hungry for this stuff,
believing that this is
what I was called to do,
but I hadn't really
been able to do it.
The church system has to change.
We have to stop being a building-focused,
Sunday service-attending institution.
People are sitting in churches,
year after year
waiting, waiting for that special minister
to come and pray for them
saying, now you have the anointing.
You can go out and you can do
this or that for God.
Or they are just sitting there,
hoping that someone
will see them,
see their talents.
And that is not what we see the
Bible telling us to do.
That is not what we see
Jesus telling us to do.
In 1995, I was working as a baker
and I didn't know anything about God.
I didn't know anything
about the Bible.
I was as a young boy in Denmark,
baptized in the Lutheran Church.
I was confirmed in the
Lutheran Church when I was fourteen.
But it was tradition.
It's tradition for many people today.
One night I looked up in the air and said,
"Come on God, are You there?
If You are there, come and take me.
I want to know You."
And a short time after,
I heard the gospel
and the fifth of April, 1995,
9:30 in the evening,
I repented
and I gave everything to Jesus.
But then I started
to come in a church.
And I started to become like
the people in the church.
And I thought it was Christianity, to
meet God and then come to a church
and sit there every Sunday.
But I got more and more frustrated.
Because I was like, "Come on, there must
be more than just going to a church,
sitting there two hours every Sunday
and listening to somebody preaching."
And at one time, I started to
just read the Book of Acts,
read about the first Christians,
how they were living.
And they didn't do the same
as I was doing.
They saw how lives got changed
where they came.
And at that time I was so frustrated,
because I had been a Christian
like many years.
But I had never healed the sick,
never cast out a demon.
I had never led anybody to Christ.
I had never experienced the life
we read about in the first church
in the Book of Acts.
So one day in frustration,
I was like,
"God, I give you everything.
I want to see this life."
And then I started to see this life,
more and more and more.
But the problem was
that in the beginning
there was nobody
who could disciple me.
There was nobody, like Jesus did
when Jesus said,
"Come and follow Me
and I will make you fishers of men."
Come and follow Me,
I will show you
how to heal the sick,
how to preach the gospel.
I will show you, train you, in how you can
be effective in the Kingdom of God.
Nobody did that.
But what is different now,
is that
now we are starting
to disciple people.
And if we take what we
have learned and give it
to the next generation of disciples
and they continue from there,
and then take that and give it
to the next generation of disciples,
in a very short time,
we will have disciples
walking around on earth,
looking exactly like Jesus,
doing the same things Jesus did.
Yes, even greater things
because He went to the Father.
I've prepared the best for you.
Yes I have prepared a place of rest.
And in that place:
Life in abundance.
In that promised land...
Now we will listen
to a friend of ours, Simon Ådahl.
In Swedish.
Sweden rules, man!
Father, I pray that
we will take Europe,
also Denmark, and Norway
and the whole world for You!
I became a Christian about
eleven years ago.
And I came into
the Swedish state church
from a totally
non-Christian background.
After a while, me and my wife,
we moved to another city
and we came into
a very big church there.
We became leaders in a big
outreach work there in church.
We were supposed to be an example
but I had never led anybody to Christ,
I had never
baptized anybody myself,
I had never seen anybody with my own eyes
who I prayed for getting healed.
I came to a point when
one night we were out
and there came a man to my table
actually, and he asked,
"Yeah, I see what you do,
I want to become a Christian.
How do I do it?"
And my reaction was,
"Okay, I pick you up tomorrow
and I bring you to church."
So I did that.
I brought him to church
and I brought him to the pastor
and the pastor led him to salvation.
But that made me react. I understood
that something was wrong,
'cause I read the Bible a lot, I went
to Bible school for a couple years
I know what the Bible said
and I was the one
who was supposed
to do these things.
I was the one who was supposed
to lay hands on the sick
and they will recover.
I was the one
who was supposed to baptize people,
and I didn't do it.
Something was wrong.
I started to think,
maybe they are lying,
maybe it's not true,
what people are telling me.
So I started to go out.
Every morning I woke up
and just prayed to the Lord.
And it was raining sometimes,
snow, bad weather,
I just went out because I was
really crying out to the Lord.
I want to know You.
I want to have the real life.
And one day I was at work and I was
reading a Christian newspaper.
There was a small note there
about a Danish man
who was in
a shopping mall in Sweden
praying for sick people
and they got healed.
And I was like, "What?"
I saw this kind of article before
but this just took my heart,
and I felt that this is God.
So I called him and he answered.
He was a normal man like me.
We spoke and I told him
about my journey
and he thought,
this is amazing, we should meet.
So I gathered a couple of friends
and we went down to him in Denmark.
Then he asked us,
"Why did you come to Denmark?"
We said,
"We want to see people get healed."
Then he said,
"Okay, in about fifteen minutes
you'll see the first person
get healed."
I was like, " yeah, yeah."
I could not believe this.
How can this be a part
of my life?
But we went out on the streets
and we came to a gang of people,
maybe about 25, 30 years old.
One of the girls had a problem
with her knee for many years.
He told me to lay my hands
on her knee
and command the pain to go away.
I almost blacked out,
I was so nervous.
And I had no faith, either, I think.
I said, okay I do it.
So I did it and she like jumped up.
"What?"
And she got healed.
And the whole crowd was like...
This rocked my world.
I just realized, this is true.
This is true.
This actually was enough for me.
I prayed for one person
and then I went by myself.
We, as Christians, are called
to make disciples.
Another word we have started
using is the word 'kickstarting'.
It's like if you have a motorbike
and you want
to start the engine,
you kickstart it.
And when that motorbike is started
you can drive all over the place.
In the same way, we as Christians
need to get kickstarted
in doing the things
Jesus has called us to.
When we, for example, kickstart
a Christian in healing the sick,
we take them out on the streets
and say, "Come and follow us."
And then we show them
how to do it.
And when they have done it one time,
they can do it again.
You say you have pain all over
your body, most in your legs?
Yeah.
And we'll pray for it; you'll see it.
I command all pain,
leave right now.
Be healed right now
in the whole body.
I command all pain,
leave the body right now.
The whole body, right now.
I pray for healing right now,
in the name of Jesus. Amen.
Just move, try to move it.
Try to feel it.
It felt good.
- It felt good, yeah?
But do you feel the pain now?
No.
- It's gone? Yeah.
People get surprised.
I command this back to be
totally restored, right now.
Bend over like this,
try to feel it.
And up again.
- For real, it is gone.
For real.
- What?
I swear.
- I am not making things up.
You can feel it. It just went away.
- Oh, yes. Oh, my God.
This is growing all over the world.
The last years we have seen
hundreds of thousands
of people getting healed.
By normal believers,
who get kickstarted
and start to go out
and heal the sick.
And those people now start
to lead other people to Christ.
So the last years we have seen
thousands of people coming to Christ.
And this is really powerful.
I came to Stockholm
and met this brother
and he was there with a bunch of guys,
and his wife was there, too.
And there we went out.
He first stopped
this person who had pain
and he placed his hand on this person,
and this person got healed.
And I was just like,
Wow, this is amazing!
This person got healed
and I was like,
now it's not on YouTube anymore.
I am not watching this on YouTube,
but now I see it in front of me.
It was amazing, seeing the reaction
of this person who got healed.
The next thing that happened was
that this lady came
and she had pain in her stomach.
This man, that was
kickstarting me was like,
Now it is your time to pray.
Just place your hand
and command the pain to go.
So I just placed my hand
and I was hesitating,
but I placed my hand
and just commanded,
"In Jesus' name, pain go."
I just removed my hand and suddenly,
you should have seen
the face of this woman.
She was like, how did you do that?
What?
Are you kidding me?
- No, we are not kidding.
This is true, and that is
why we do this.
No.
This is sick.
Jesus healed you, not me.
Wow, I have never been
in such a thing before,
and my dreams just
came true, right there.
This is actually
the best day of my life.
Being part of what I have been
longing for, for such a long time.
So on my way back home
I was so filled up with joy.
So I was sitting in the bus
going home.
When I arrived, I could not
just sit or just like go home.
I just went around in the city downtown
and I was praying for people
and the very same day,
and I came across these girls
that I prayed for and they
got healed instantly as well.
I was like, Wow!
So this is not something that happened
in Stockholm and stayed there.
It continues, you know.
Ever since then, I was
going out every day.
Every day I was out on the streets and
I've seen thousands getting healed.
It just changed me.
It changed the entire me.
It's, WOW!
Move your leg.
I do not feel anything.
It disappeared?
I cannot feel it.
- No.
Is it not strange?
- Yes.
It was Jesus who healed you.
Bend over and try to feel it.
It worked, Dennis.
- Try it. Try it.
How does it feel now?
- It feels perfect.
All pain is gone?
- All pain is totally gone.
I swear to God.
Thank you, Jesus.
I was not expecting what we saw,
I kinda was... this is supposed to happen.
I have seen it happen
in videos all the time
but I've never been able
to do it myself
and I fully expected
that this is what God does.
This is what He uses me for.
This is my purpose here.
We prayed for one girl
who had some issues with the back.
I think she had
some kind of surgery.
Pain, go right now.
Back, go in place right now,
in the name of Jesus.
I don't know if you feel
something happening.
Oh, snap.
- Wow, something happened.
She got filled with the Holy Spirit
and God met her in a radical way.
She was in tears.
- She fell down in front of us.
Fill her up.
More, more.
The Holy Spirit is over you,
just open your mouth.
Holy Spirit, more, more, more.
Fill her up.
You just got baptized,
filled with the Spirit.
He is there, He is there.
This is a new beginning.
It's a new beginning for you.
It's a new beginning.
God, we thank You for freedom.
God, we thank You for a new beginning.
Her family that was with her,
her sister-in-law and her kids,
were just totally at peace;
like everything's normal, and
people walking by,
"What's going on?"
And I just remember thinking,
This is so cool, what's happening
to this girl right now.
She had no idea what would
happen that day.
She got back up and you could
tell she was a different person.
God had changed her
from the inside out.
I'm okay, Lillia, I'm okay.
This is good.
- Way more than okay.
Way better than just okay.
God, He wants to be alive.
He wants to show us
and show who He is to us.
And see, this is God.
This is outside here.
Not in a fine church,
but God is there
and He wants to be part
of our life.
He wants to be part of your life.
Then we moved on from there.
Then we prayed for
a guy named Danny.
Right, first we asked for
another guy if he had any pain.
He said, "No."
And then Danny came.
Right. We asked a gentleman
on a bench if we could pray.
He said, "No, no, no, I'm okay."
And a guy named Danny said,
"Oh, my back really hurts."
- "For how long?"
"For ten years."
Actually it was five years
that this man's back hurt.
And so we said,
"Okay cool, well let's sit you down."
And we sat him down
and his one leg was longer than
the other by about half an inch.
Leg grow, loosen and grow
right now in the name of Jesus.
There it is.
- Yeah, whoa, there is movement.
Did you feel that?
- And it moved in your hands.
Something popped
when it came out.
Danny, try to stand up
and feel your back now.
That is pretty good.
- Is it gone?
Yeah.
- Fifteen years, and it's gone.
Yeah, well five.
- Oh, five years, and it's gone now.
What did you experience?
- I don't know, I felt it's good.
This is the first time
he does this.
That was awesome, and while
looking for more people
we decided to go get some ice cream.
We went in and you talked to
the lady behind the counter.
There was a woman
behind the counter
and she asked what we were doing,
where we were from, and
so we explained to her,
"Oh, we're going around and praying.
I am from Houston and we
are with people from all over
and we're praying for people
with sickness or pain."
She said, "Really?"
I told about Danny.
She said, "Oh my gosh,
I want to meet this guy."
I thought she meant Danny,
who got healed.
"I don't know where he is, sorry."
She said, "Whenever he comes
back to pray, you let me know."
In my mind, I thought,
"That was me! I'm right here."
So, yeah I'll come back,
just a minute.
And she came around the
counter and took off her shoe.
"It is this ankle."
She opened up
and I continued praying for her.
It got better and better.
I turn around and there
are 4 or 5 people saying,
"I have pain."
"Could you pray for me?"
How is it?
- What are you doing?
It wasn't me, man.
- I was in pain.
I'm not lying.
Is it gone completely?
Come on, jump, jump!
- I can do it now.
What are you doing? Jesus.
- It's Jesus.
Go down, go down, go down!
When could you do that last time?
In the military.
- Ten years ago?
Yeah, ten years ago.
- So you couldn't do this for ten years?
No. Every time I can't.
Come on!
- No, I know it feels good.
Sit in the chair.
See if you can do this quick as usual.
And then stand up.
If this is God, then...
I love you.
It is God! Ten years you have
not been able to do that.
No, I haven't;
I've been in pain,
always going to the
doctors, in & out.
But Jesus is the great Doctor.
He is the highest and He is there.
He is. Amen.
What is wrong with you?
- My arm.
You cannot lift it
higher than that? No.
How long have you had that?
- Like six weeks.
So in six weeks you have not
been able to do like this.
Be loosened right now
in the name of Jesus, right now.
You got it!
You got it.
It's yours, keep it.
Before you could get to here
and it would hurt, right?
Moving better, yeah?
It's good.
- Up with your hand!
Give me five.
You feel good?
Now we know what it's like.
Yeah.
So we get to go back to Houston
and go find parks and stores.
When we eat pizza somewhere...
that's not off-limits for God.
Yeah, it is like a redhead
growing up in Asia thinking,
"I feel like there has to be more
in life. Everybody is the same."
and then going to Ireland.
"There is, there really is!
There are people like me!"
That is how I feel, like,
"Oh, this is life, okay good."
That is what I wanted,
and now I can go and do that.
Yeah, so we are excited
to go back and I just feel like...
Man! My neighbors, the people, they have
no idea what is about to hit them.
Because I get it now, I can do this.
God, I can absolutely do this.
We're living in
really exciting times in Europe,
we're beginning to see a reenactment
of the Book of Acts in our times.
We're seeing that people
are going out with the gospel,
with the demonstration
of the Kingdom.
And it is often
a very clear gospel message,
about turning away
from one's sins, and
part of the package is actually
baptism and being filled
with the Holy Spirit.
So often in our church systems
they are separated.
But what we are seeing
more and more,
it's coming together
into one stream,
like it was in the Book of Acts.
So there's no waiting.
So when somebody repents
and expresses faith in Jesus,
they are taken
wherever there is water.
And it can be anywhere;
it can be a lake,
it can be in a rainwater tub,
it can be in a bath, or wherever.
People are baptized immediately
and at the same time,
also filled with the Holy Spirit.
The first words that
came out of Jesus' mouth, were,
"Repent, the Kingdom of God is near."
And we are called
to preach repentance today.
And it's like that part has been lost
in the church today.
We are talking about faith,
but we do not talk about repentance.
They are almost afraid
to talk about sin.
But we are called
We are called to preach repentance.
We have to say what sin is.
We have to say that those people
who continue in sin,
are going to die.
We have to talk about sin
before we talk about
that Jesus was the Lamb of God,
who came to remove our sin.
Because if we don't talk about sin,
what should people then do with Jesus?
Where are you going?
- I go with God, to heaven.
Why?
- Because...
Are you a good person?
- Yeah.
Have you ever lied?
Have you ever stolen anything?
Downloaded something without paying?
- Yes.
Have you had sex outside of marriage?
These are three
of the ten commandments.
How many shall I go through?
It's all about how we compare
ourselves to each other.
Of course, if you compare yourself
to people around you,
you can think
you are a good person.
The question is not if you
think you're a good person.
The question is,
Are you good enough?
The Bible says, if you have just
done one of the sins,
you are guilty of them all.
It's not like in other things,
like it's okay if you weigh
and you have bad deeds
and the good...
It is not like that.
It is guilty or not guilty.
If you have once broken the law,
you are guilty of breaking the law.
If we talk about God,
no person can ever
come to God, come to heaven
by our good deeds.
It is not possible.
And I have always thought
I was a good person because,
yes, I have been
fighting a little too much,
I have been drinking too much.
I have been doing things, but...
this person and this person
is much worse than me.
So my problem was that I compared
myself to people around me,
instead of comparing myself
to the One
I am going to stand
in front of one day.
I believe we have to get back
to what the Bible shows us.
Repentance isn't so much
feeling sorry about our sins
and what we've done
and how we've violated God's Word,
in the sense of ourselves.
Being sorry is not true repentance.
It's part of it,
but it is not the full story.
We see Pharaoh in the Old Testament
with the Israelites in Egypt.
He was sorry. He proclaimed,
"Oh, I have sinned against God."
So he confessed his sin, but he
did not turn away from his sin.
Neither is it just remorse.
A lot of people say that,
"You see, they're really sorry;
they're crying
because they have true remorse."
Judas in the New Testament,
he had remorse.
He was so remorseful
that he actually committed suicide,
but he did not
turn away from his sin.
When we read the Bible, we can
see that God brackets repentance
with forgiveness,
rather than forgiveness
with faith in Jesus.
And I think, looking at it in
the latter part, we often think that
with faith in Jesus, God
automatically forgives us our sins.
And as you read the Bible,
you discover that's not the case.
Let's imagine you and me
play chess together.
I move, and then it's your turn.
I want to see you move.
My turn. Your turn.
Am I now allowed to do this?
Move one there, and one there.
Am I allowed to move two times?
- No.
Why? Because there are rules.
And the rules are that you move
one time, then I move one time.
When it comes to God,
you have sinned.
You have done something
that's wrong
and because of that,
you are divided from God.
You can not have fellowship with God
because of our sin.
Our sin causes that God
cannot have fellowship with us.
God is looking at you and says,
"I don't want to punish you,
but I am holy, so I need to do it."
"But at the same time, I want
to give you a chance
to get forgiveness
and get a relationship with Me,
so I sent my son, Jesus,
to die for you."
So it's like this.
You have sinned and broke
the commandments of God.
That's why we are living
without fellowship with God.
We are living our own life,
divided from God.
God looked down on you and said,
"I don't want to judge you,
I want to forgive you, so I send
my son, Jesus, to die for you."
Whose turn is it now?
Your turn.
God wants to forgive.
He wants to set you free.
He wants to give you a new life
and heal through you.
He wants to do those things,
but he says,
"Move, it is your turn!"
He is waiting for you to do it.
But as soon as you say, I repent,
and receive that forgiveness.
As soon as you do this,
God is like, "I'm going to forgive you."
It is so important
to understand,
because there's so many people...
I had that at one time.
Like you, I believed
there was a God.
But in my mind, in my universe,
"Okay, when it's time,
He will come to me.
It's up to Him.
He's great. He can do
it when he wants to."
And I moved the responsibility
from me over to Him.
A true deep repentance
requires action.
It's not just a word; it's
not just something that we think.
True repentance is
not only realizing
that you have sinned
against a holy God,
but that you then
confess your sins to him,
you are remorseful to Him,
and you turn away
from that sinful life
and you start living His life.
The word for repent in the Bible
is the word 'metanoia'
which means to 'again think'.
And God wants us to think again.
About our lives
and how we've lived.
If we will have a rethink about God
and how our sins affect Him,
then God will also have a rethink
about what he thinks about us.
And if you confess your sin
and get it out in the light,
you experience forgiveness.
But if you keep it close,
every time you take a step
toward the light,
Satan is going to say,
"But remember, but remember..."
- Yes, that's what he does.
But now it's out.
You have confessed it.
You have said it to me;
you have said it.
Be led by the Holy Spirit; maybe you
should say it to the whole world.
I don't know what,
but there is forgiveness.
People need to hear this.
There is freedom.
There's so many girls
going through it, so many women.
And they have done exactly the same,
carried it around,
thirty, forty, fifty years.
This is not where freedom is.
Freedom is what you
experience, right now.
I came today, seeking God
for the gift of tongues.
And for anything else in my life
that I may need deliverance from.
And over this weekend,
God has delivered me
and blessed me
with the gift of tongues,
and washed me with water baptism.
I've been living
for over thirty years
with shame and embarrassment,
as a secret...
that when I was in my twenties
I had an abortion.
And each and every day
from that day forward,
the devil has had his way with me.
So I've been seeking God, too,
as I was watching Torben's videos.
Telling God,
I can't do it anymore.
Pleading, asking,
wanting to know
if He had forgiveness for me.
And then it came that He
led me to come here this weekend.
And I felt led to speak with Torben,
that God had something to say
through him to me.
So, I was given the opportunity
by God to be freed.
Delivered from this pain.
Over thirty years, I am free.
Thank you, Jesus. Thank you.
Be free.
...that when I was in my twenties...
God help me... He has!
I had an abortion
and ever since that day,
God has tried to
tell me it's okay,
but the devil just had
that greater hold on my life.
He just kept hanging on
and hanging in.
I remember the day
it happened like yesterday
and I feel the pain the same.
It's a new beginning.
It's a new start.
Are you ready to get
baptized to Jesus Christ
to wash away your sins?
- Yes.
So, on your own faith,
we baptize you to Jesus Christ.
Die with Christ.
Up with Christ.
Yay!
Free!
Yes!
Come, let's pray for you.
God, we thank You for Elizabeth.
God, we thank You for your freedom.
And when she confessed that,
another woman came up
and confessed the same sin.
And suddenly, her testimony
already brought life and
forgiveness to another.
And that woman, there,
got baptized in water
and she experienced that freedom.
Later we were at a meeting
with eighty people,
where she explained
how she had done that,
and it was sin, with the abortion,
but Jesus had forgiven her her sins.
When she confessed that,
and shared that testimony
at a meeting with eighty people,
out of that meeting, there came
twelve women to her afterwards
confessing the same.
And here we see the power
in confessing sins,
the power of baptism in water,
and what the gospel is all about.
"He who believes and is baptized
shall be saved," Jesus said.
What's really interesting
about water baptism is that...
I believe that through
time and tradition
today, we look at a sacrament
very different
than what the Bible shows us
a sacrament really is.
Often we look at a sacrament as an
outward sign of an inward reality.
And what's interesting
about that definition
is that it takes the spiritual
and the physical
and it completely separates
these two things.
And as a result,
we only see baptism
as something that's
just ceremonial
and has no connection with
anything in the spiritual realm.
In other words, it's
just like a confirmation
of something that's
already taken place in the spirit.
But baptism is very,
very different from that.
What we've discovered,
is that baptism
is not something
that's just sacramental,
as far as being an outward sign
of an inward reality.
We're seeing that when
you go into that water,
the Spirit of God is touching that.
And when the physical and the
spiritual connect in water baptism,
God does something miraculous.
What's interesting is that
water baptism is two things.
It's both a bath and a burial.
And to have a bath,
you have to be dirty!
So, what does that mean?
It means that a person
who's getting baptized
needs to acknowledge
their sins before God.
And in that sense, baptism
and repentance go hand in hand.
It's turning
and coming in faith.
And the requirement for baptism,
what God wants us to bring,
is repentance
and faith in Jesus Christ.
A person comes,
dead in their sins,
and what happens is
we take that person,
who's coming in his sins,
bringing proof of repentance,
and then we baptize him.
So when that person comes out,
they are brand new and clean.
I tell many people that we meet,
water baptism isn't
just a clean start off.
It is a brand new,
clean life to start.
Let it out, let it out.
More, more.
Glory, glory.
Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Jesus. Thank you, Jesus.
Praise your name. Thank you, Jesus.
Thank you, Jesus.
How do you feel?
I was feeling like something
went out of...
Welling up; it's the living water
that's welling up inside of you
and God is releasing that
through your mouth.
Claudio, you are a brand new man.
- Amen.
You feel good?
- Yeah.
This is just
the beginning, Claudio.
This is just the beginning.
- Yes.
God's given you this gift now.
There's gonna be times where you
may not know what to pray for.
And now you can go
in faith and pray.
You know what's great about
praying in tongues is
that I can concentrate
on other things while praying
because my mind is not praying.
I'm just letting my mouth
move by faith.
And the Spirit intercedes
through us.
So God just used you.
The Spirit came in
and intercedes through you.
It's beautiful.
- Amen. Thanks, God.
Isn't God good?
- Yes.
He's great.
- Yes, He is.
I've learned something today.
The power of water baptism
unto Jesus.
It is no longer like a symbol,
like most churches might believe,
like I used to believe,
because that's all I knew.
I just thought it was something
you just go through
with a sprinkle or whatever.
But there's so much power
when you truly believe
what it's all about.
About the death, the burial,
the closure, the old man,
the nature is gone,
and a new man comes up.
As I've learned today,
do you believe
in Jesus as your
Lord and Savior?
Yes, I do.
Well, the old man goes under,
you die, and a new man arises.
And as soon as he came up
out of the water,
he said something left him.
A great weight left him and
no longer had any hold on his life.
And immediately he received
the baptism of the Holy Spirit.
And this brother was so broken,
he was sobbing.
He was just holding his chest.
It was so precious to see.
It was so precious to see
what God was doing in his life.
And all he could do was just weep
in the presence of God.
And for me, just to see
what God had...
He drove, I guess
three, four hours to get here
because this is what he wanted.
And that thing that was
attacking him all this time
no longer has power over him,
and he is free. He is totally free.
And I am truly thankful.
So now I have learned
that there is something
to water baptism,
there is something
to repentance,
there is something to having
the baptism with the Holy Spirit.
All three things are needed.
And that has truly
changed my life.
And now I preach that message
until the day I die.
Because I have experienced it,
and it was one of the most powerful
demonstrations of God's love
that I have ever seen.
The reason why I believe
we're seeing this happen now
is because when
that old man dies,
demons lose their grip
and their grab.
They can no longer
torment a dead man.
Because the old man dies.
And when you come
out of that water,
you're somebody brand new.
There's a new man
wearing your old clothes.
When Jesus was
walking here on earth,
He was preaching repentance.
And then He was teaching that
people need to be born again,
out of water and Spirit.
But He could not, at that time,
baptize people in His name.
He could not baptize people
with the Holy Spirit.
But after the cross,
when Peter stood up on Pentecost,
we hear the full gospel for
the first time, when Peter said,
"Repent, get baptized for the
forgiveness of your sins,
and you will receive
the Holy Spirit."
Okay, you kneel down and you say,
"I baptize you to Jesus Christ"
and make sure he goes down.
Die with Christ.
Up with Christ.
Freedom! Freedom!
Go! Go!
Come! Leave! Go! Go! Go!
I command you, spirit go!
Right now! Come out!
Go! In the name of Jesus,
I command this spirit, go!
Leave him, right now!
Out! Out!
Go!
In the name of Jesus, I command
every demon, go, right now!
Go! Right now!
Come out!
I command this demon, go!
Go, right now!
Demon, go!
I command every demon,
leave him right now!
Lie, go! Come out!
More, more. Let it go!
I command you, demon,
in the name of Jesus, come out!
Get out! More!
Go! Go! Go!
In the name of Jesus,
I command the last thing to go!
Go! In the name of Jesus,
every demon, come out!
Right now!
Leave him! Leave him!
Fill him up! Fill him up! More!
Freedom! Freedom!
This is real.
Thank you.
This is real!
If you want to read a book about
this, I want to recommend a book.
Maybe you have heard about it.
The name of the book is the Bible.
This is what
we read in the Bible.
He got set free and then
the Holy Spirit took over.
It's not just a picture;
it's real.
And if this is real in the Bible,
what about the rest?
Every word is real,
from the beginning to the end.
Hallelujah!
My friend!
I still remember
clenching my fists,
and I remember
banging on the water,
and then I was really
yelling out loud, and then
there was a commotion,
something happening.
I didn't know it was me.
I didn't know what was happening.
I had my eyes closed,
and then I opened my eyes,
and I was in a different position
to where I was before.
I was looking,
and Torben was over there,
and I was facing this way, and
before, I was facing the other way.
I didn't quite understand why.
And then there was
some more commotion.
The last thing I remember
was Torben saying,
"Demons, get out."
It was peaceful then;
it just calmed down.
There was quietness and silence.
I can remember looking up
and there were loads of people
with all their cameras out.
Many people looked at me
and it was like
I was in a bit of a shock.
Like coming out of a surgery
and everyone's there.
In terms of how
I can explain it,
through my life
and my experiences,
there's not anything
that's close to this.
But the best thing I have
from my experience
is it's like having
a tooth taken out.
I knew there was
something in there
when this commotion was going on,
that had no right to be there.
It's like now that
that tooth has come out,
and there's nothing there.
It has come out. Gone.
And there's like new skin there.
When you have
your tooth taken out,
you want to get your tongue
and you want to touch it.
You just creep your tongue over
to where the tooth has come out,
to feel what it is like,
and it was like that.
There was something
new and young there,
where this tooth had been.
And I'm happy I'm free,
thanks to Jesus Christ.
As soon as people get baptized,
I start to pray for them
for deliverance because now
they have died with Christ,
they have risen up with Christ,
so now Satan has to leave them.
And it's really strong
to see deliverance
out there as part of baptism.
And it was so powerful.
So many people came and saw it
and suddenly there was a multitude
of 150, 200 people looking on.
Right after he got set free,
he got baptized with the Holy Spirit
and spoke in tongues.
It was really powerful.
Then we were supposed to baptize
the rest of his family: his son
and his daughter, and his wife.
When they came down in
the water, ready to get baptized,
God did something amazing.
We read in the gospels today
that Jesus got baptized
in the river Jordan.
We read the bit when the heavens opened
and the Holy Spirit
came down like a dove.
Me and Lauren,
we were just saying,
"Shall we pray that something
like that happens today?
That we see a sign in the sky
when we get baptized?"
So when we got baptized,
I was in the water
waiting to get baptized,
and I heard people in
the crowd saying, "Look up!"
And I turned and I looked up and
saw 'real' written in the sky.
And it was like my prayer
had been answered
as I was about to get baptized.
Thank you, Jesus.
Everybody pointed and said,
"Look, look up!"
And up in the sky,
there had just been an airplane
writing in the sky, 'real'.
And it was in the same time
that I was praying for her husband
and he got delivered,
and I had been saying,
"This is real.
This is not a picture."
"If this is real. Everything we
read in the Bible is real."
And suddenly we saw it,
in the sky,
that God had written, 'real'.
real
Torben, look up!
- Yeah, I have seen it.
Yeah, I see it.
We started to preach
the gospel afterwards
and many more people
repented and got saved that day.
Instead of just baptizing eight
people as we were supposed to,
we baptized more
than thirty people.
Because people who
saw what happened,
saw how people
got delivered from demons,
saw how they
received the Holy Spirit,
they also repented
from their sins
and came and got baptized
and experienced the same.
The demonic world is so real.
It's very real.
I have seen glimpses
of it in churches
when evangelists had come,
or so-called "men of God" had come,
people who walk in authority.
They pray for people
and see them manifest.
But I had never seen it happen
from my own hand.
The first real experience I had
and probably
the biggest experience
is when my wife and I
baptized someone
for the first time in our home.
This person, she was involved in
New Age: Reiki healing,
tarot card reading, crystals,
a lot of New Age things.
We baptized her and if we had
just left it at that
like a normal church service,
we would have smiled,
given her a certificate and
had a cup of coffee afterwards.
But we continued to
pray for her, and pray for her,
and after about two minutes,
the demons started to manifest.
And one after one, they manifest
and we cast them out.
And it was the most real,
the most radical experience,
that I've ever had.
It opened my eyes up
to the battle. This is a fight.
We are not just asked,
we are not told it's a good idea,
but we are commanded by Jesus
to cast out demons.
We're given the responsibility
to set people free in Jesus' name.
Why is there a fight going on?
Because Satan don't like it.
But now we are going
under water and then
she's going to come up
and you are going to see
a freedom. You are going to see
a freedom and a new life.
Just kneel down.
Don't be afraid. Kneel down.
- I cannot.
No, you can, you can.
In the name of Jesus,
you can, you can.
It's a new life.
Satan is a liar. Satan is a liar.
He has been lying
and he don't want you
to give everything over
to Jesus Christ.
Because when you give yourself
over, he will set you free
and Satan is going to lose
and he don't want this.
You can.
My knees don't want to bend.
Go down, in the name of Jesus.
She wants to, but her knees
don't want to bend.
She cannot get down.
There is a fight going on.
In Jesus' name,
God, we thank you.
Just go down, in the name of Jesus,
just go down.
Down, down, just go down,
in the name of Jesus.
In the name of Jesus.
In the name of Jesus, go down.
Go down, go down.
Are you ready to get baptized
to Jesus Christ?
So on your own faith
we baptize you to Jesus Christ.
Just go down. Die with Christ.
Up with Christ.
Freedom! Freedom! Satan, go!
Leave her! Leave her, right now!
Come out! Come out!
Leave him! Go!
Come out! Go!
Right now!
Loose! Loose!
Go! Go! In the name of Jesus,
I command this religious spirit,
go, right now,
in the name of Jesus!
Go! Last thing, go!
Go! Go, in the name of Jesus!
Go! Right now!
Go! Go!
Get out, in the name of Jesus!
Get out!
Go! Right now! Come out!
Every anger, every fear,
go right now, in the name of Jesus!
Come out! Right now!
Get out! Get out now!
Come out, right now!
I command you, go!
Go! Go right now!
Freedom! Right now!
Let it go!
I command this demon, go!
I command this spirit to go!
Get out! Get out! Just now!
Go, in the name of Jesus!
Go right now, in the name of Jesus!
Get out right now!
Go! Go! I command every demon,
leave him right now!
Come out!
Go, right now in Jesus' name!
Come out, right now!
Go! Go!
Go, in the name of Jesus!
I command every spirit, leave him.
Right now! Right now! Come out!
Get out! Get out!
Get out right now in Jesus' name.
Come out! Come out!
Hallelujah.
Can you experience a freedom?
You are free.
How is it?
- It's great, thank you!
Come on, a new life.
Come on, can you see it?
I love it!
Come on friends, can you see it?
This is the power in baptism.
Repent from your sins,
towards Jesus Christ.
It is a battle.
But Satan has lost.
Jesus is alive.
A new life, a new life.
Freedom.
- Yes.
Praise the Lord.
Praise Jesus.
Thank you that you are filling her up.
Thank you, thank you.
Amen!
You got the Holy Spirit.
- Yeah.
He has never spoken
in tongues before now.
Powerful!
We have seen so many people
got delivered from sin
in baptism.
We have seen
schizophrenic people
get delivered from demons
in baptism.
We have seen people
with eating disorders
get delivered in baptism.
We have seen sick people
get healed in baptism.
We have seen many people
who were not able before
to receive the baptism
with the Holy Spirit.
But when they
got baptized in water,
the Holy Spirit came over them
and they started to speak in tongues.
It is real. I tell you, it is real.
I don't know how to explain it,
but the Spirit of God came
and I was really baptized in the
Spirit. I really spoke in tongues.
I'm going to pray
and you are going to help me.
What is your name?
- Kathy.
Kathy has anxiety and she also wants
to get baptized with the Holy Spirit.
We just met and I talked about baptism
with the Holy Spirit and how it is.
God,
I believe in you.
I believe in you, Jesus.
I repent.
And I ask you,
set me free
from every anxiety
and come with your Holy Spirit.
Fill me up.
Baptize me.
Right now.
In the name of Jesus.
The Bible is clear that
there is always a sign
when people receive
the baptism with the Holy Spirit.
In the Book of Acts, chapter 8,
we can read about Philip,
how he came to Samaria
and he preached the gospel.
And people received the message
and they repented
and they got baptized
in water to Jesus Christ.
But at that time
they had not yet
received the baptism
with the Holy Spirit.
So when the Apostles
came, they saw
that they have not received the
baptism with the Holy Spirit.
So they laid their hands on them
and they received the baptism
with the Holy Spirit.
You don't read
right there what happened,
but you know there was a sign.
Why?
Because there was a guy, Simon.
Simon, he saw how
the Holy Spirit was given
by the hands of the apostles.
And when he saw that,
he wanted the same power,
that those people on which
he would lay his hands
would also receive
the Holy Spirit.
Now we start to speak
in tongues, when I say, "Now"
just say the first words
and let it out.
Now.
Holy Spirit, freedom.
Freedom, right now.
Freedom, freedom.
Holy Spirit, freedom.
Freedom, right now.
Come with your strength, right now.
Strength, strength.
Yeah, it's cool, isn't it?
I had mine done yesterday.
He got baptized with
the Holy Spirit yesterday
and you, today.
I have never spoken
in tongues before.
How? It just came?
- Yeah.
How was that?
That was awesome;
that's crazy amazing.
Try to imagine that
here in the middle of the street.
That's awesome, thank you.
Thank you so much.
You go and tell others
now about this.
I have always felt that if there
are two camps;
if you go to one camp they only
talk about miracles, miracles.
That didn't seem to make
a lot of sense to me
for the simple reason that
if Jesus only wanted
to help us with miracles
and healing my physical body,
and that's all he wanted to do,
then it kind of contradicts
this whole aspect of
God promising to give us believers
a new body one day.
But at the same time, if I go
to the other side of the camp
and I say miracles are not for
today, it's only the Word of God,
then it contradicts Scripture
because the Scripture says that
the Word will come with power
and He'll confirm it with power.
So where is that middle road?
And the middle road is found
in the Word of God,
where there is
a balance of both;
where we want the Word of God
to come together
with the power of God
and actually make a
transformation in people's lives,
where people will truly be
convicted by the Holy Spirit,
experience a new life,
repent, turn from sin,
not just confess sin,
but forsake sin,
receive the power of God,
be baptized in water,
speak in tongues,
and operate on a
day-to-day basis
with the power of God in you
or rather, in the temple,
which is us.
For years, I just goofed
around with religion.
Then I moved away
from it completely,
and then there was this hunger
to come back to it.
And as I came back, I realized
there were areas in my life
where I was shut down
in unbelief.
That doesn't happen for today;
that was only in Jesus' time,
or that's only meant for a few people.
Then I read the Bible
and it says,
"These signs will follow
those who believe."
And I'm saying," I am a believer,
why is it not happening?"
And what we need is
to stir each other's faith.
If I have a team of people
and all doing the same thing,
I get encouraged in my faith.
The same with you now.
Today you have a
gift of a language.
If you don't use that gift,
guess what will happen?
It will fall away.
What will happen if you
have this in you now
and you are not going
to read your Bible?
You will throw it all away.
Cultivate it;
make it your lifestyle.
Make God the center of your life
and do what we are doing
to your friends.
Think of anyone you know,
any one of your friends.
Call them and tell them
what happened.
Share your testimony
and then you pray for them.
Believe that when you put your
hand to pray,
I am talking with confidence. Guess
how long have I been doing this?
Since yesterday.
- Today.
Today is my first day healing people.
I am praying for healing today.
Now just imagine,
all that church junk we learned,
and I could never do anything.
And now with the power
of God in us,
you can do it right now,
and actually
look for somebody, pray for them
and you will have a healing.
That's the power of Jesus Christ.
He is amazing!
Come on, all come together.
Watch what's happening.
You will see what
God is going to do.
Is that awesome?
- Yeah.
Who wants to come first,
who has got a problem?
No, no, really.
- You have got blisters, right now.
Okay.
- You have got pain in the ankle?
No, on my foot,
I have got blisters everywhere.
Okay.
Be healed, in Jesus' name.
How do you feel?
Move your leg.
Oh, my God.
No, I don't feel anything.
- Really?
On a scale of one to ten,
do you feel any pain?
Only two.
- Okay, let's pray again.
Bones, come into alignment.
Be healed, in Jesus' name.
I don't feel anything.
That's crazy.
It is!
Isn't Jesus awesome?
He is amazing, isn't He?
- I love Him.
Thank you so much.
- Are you sure?
You are not just saying this to please me?
- No, I am being legit.
I can actually walk.
- Fantastic. Walk and show me. Come on.
No pain at all?
Fabulous.
Praise Jesus, praise Him.
Who is the next?
I have joint pains in my knee.
Right.
- Yeah.
How long have you had it for?
It started about the middle of
last year and it comes and goes.
What would you say
is the pain level now?
Can you feel any pain?
When I put pressure on it.
Okay, let's pray.
Knees, joints be healed,
in Jesus' name.
Move it now
and see how you feel.
Just move it around.
That's a bit funny.
It was there two seconds ago
and now it doesn't hurt.
At all? Completely?
At all. I'm putting
pressure on it.
If I put pressure on it
normally I feel like...
Is it completely gone?
- Yeah.
Praise God for that.
You know how this
healing happened?
By the power of Jesus.
It's Jesus that does it, not me.
I am not any special person;
I am just a messenger.
Anyone else has got anything?
Come on.
I recently recovered
from a sprained ankle
and still get pain
every now and again.
Do you have it right now?
- A little bit.
Move it around and see
what kind of pain you have.
Yeah, I have got pain.
- Okay.
Ankles, be healed,
in the name of Jesus.
Move your ankle.
- That feels weird.
Come on, walk a little bit.
That's so...
- Isn't He amazing?
I am as amazed as you,
because you know what?
I am a new Christian.
I have just been baptized in water.
I have just received
the baptism of the Holy Spirit.
I spoke in a foreign language,
just like the Bible says.
Then the Bible says,
go out and heal people.
Don't listen to the religious
denominations of Christianity.
That's all rubbish.
That's all religion.
True followers of Christ
do what Jesus tells us to do,
and that's what we do.
We are simple, ordinary people,
just going out and
listening to what Jesus says.
How much do you know
about the Holy Spirit?
And baptism with the Holy Spirit?
- He intercedes for me.
Have you heard about speaking in tongues?
I have; I have seen it
when I was younger
but I got really scared,
so I wasn't sure what it was,
with very little understanding
about the Bible
and how the Holy Spirit works.
It was kind of hard for me
to understand, but
in the church that I go to
I have not seen it happening yet.
In the Book of Acts, chapter 19,
you read about Paul,
how he came to Ephesus,
where he met some believers.
He did not ask them
which church they attended,
because this is not important.
He asked them,
"Did you receive the Holy Spirit
when you believed?"
And those believers had not yet
got baptized in water
in the name of Jesus Christ
and they had not yet
received the Holy Spirit.
So Paul, there baptized
them to Jesus Christ
and when he then laid
the hands on them,
they all received the Holy Spirit
and started speaking in tongues.
Freedom. Freedom. More.
More freedom. Freedom, right now.
God, we thank you for your love.
We thank you for your freedom.
Thank you Holy Spirit that you are
filling her up. You are filling her up.
Never the same, never the same.
How are you?
You felt that... God...
You have never experienced that?
I will never be the same.
And there in that mall,
I laid the hands on her
and the Holy Spirit
came over her.
She had never experienced
that before.
She was so touched
by the Holy Spirit,
so we decided to go outside
to talk and pray a little more.
Outside, when I prayed for her,
a demon started to manifest.
I command this spirit,
go right now!
I command this,
leave her, right now!
There is freedom.
Come out! Go!
Freedom, right now.
Go!
Go, I command this spirit, go!
Go! Go! Right now! Go!
Leave her! Leave her!
Right now! Leave her!
In the beginning, I did not know
exactly what I was praying for,
but then God revealed it to me.
He showed me a sin in her life
that she had done.
When I told her that,
she broke down crying
and said, "How did you know,
how did you know this?
Can God forgive me?"
There, outside that mall
that young girl met God.
It was so strong.
So at one point,
there came three guards
running out and she said,
"Go away, go away,
I want to talk with them.
I want to talk with them."
And that day, that girl met God.
Later in the afternoon, she came
and we prayed for her
and she got baptized with the
Holy Spirit and spoke in tongues.
It was very emotional.
And when he was praying for me,
I have never mentioned it
to him before
but he did tell me
that I reminded him of
someone who was going
through the same thing.
And that's when I knew that God
wanted to tell me that day
that He has forgiven me.
Even though, I didn't want
to forgive myself
because I thought there is
no forgiveness for such thing.
But that day, God used Torben
to let me know that
He loves me and He forgave me
from what I have done.
And He has allowed me
to experience that.
I will never forget it and
I will never be the same again.
Can you tell about yesterday
and then what happened today?
- Yeah.
Sorry, I'm just really happy.
I thought about it yesterday.
It really is His way
of telling me.
Because I was tired
of looking for answers
and I could not
find it anywhere.
There was always
something inside me.
Yesterday it was finalized for me
and I am just really happy for it.
So today I got baptized.
I felt really great after.
It's something that I have been
thinking of doing before
but I thought that there are
things I have to do first
before I can do it.
I have to talk to a pastor,
have a couple of seminars
or something like that,
So, on your own faith
we baptize you to Jesus Christ.
Die with Christ.
Up with Christ.
God, we thank you for Maria.
We thank you for everything
you have done, God.
Thank you for what
you did yesterday and today.
Thank you for what you
are going to do in the future, God.
It's so amazing, how God
really answers prayers
and how He can give you,
in His perfect time,
the things that you
need to learn
and the things you need
to know about His love.
I was actually praying
the night before I met Torben.
I was praying that night on the
highway while I was driving.
I was praying that I would have
this desire in my heart
to know Him and to reach out
and just give everything to Him,
but I didn't know
where to start.
I felt like I've ran away so far
that... He's not there anymore.
But yesterday He
answered my prayer
and He made me realize
that He was there the entire time.
He was right there, when I
was grieving, when I was depressed.
Depression got me big.
But I'm still here and I'm
a representation of His love.
I really think that when
the church comes back
to a true baptism,
the true gospel:
Repent, turn to Christ.
Be baptized for the
remission of your sins.
Die with Christ
and rise with Christ
and be filled
with the Holy Spirit.
That would change this world.
What we see in the Book of Acts
is an organic, dynamic
life with God
that is not based on hierarchy.
It's not based on programs
or projects.
It's people
who are following Jesus.
As we are living the
Book of Acts,
we are now seeing
how that plays out in life.
And now, when we look into
that perfect mirror of God's Word,
where it says,
"The Word became flesh."
It's happening in our own lives.
So it's like, we are now looking at
ourselves when we read Scripture.
I see people
who are fed up with structure.
who are fed up with traditions.
I see people who will not
accept anything but the truth.
Almost every Christian in the world
wants to see a revival.
But my picture
of revival was like,
some angels from heaven will come,
or a light, and everyone gets started
and just wake up,
and then we have the revival.
But, what we see today is that
when all Christians on this planet
get activated, start doing
the things the Bible says
we are going to do:
go out, heal the sick,
preach the gospel, lead people
to Christ; then we have the revival.
I believe that the revival has been here
since Jesus came 2000 years ago.
I truly believe
this is the last reformation,
the last reformation
of the church.
This stuff is real. It's real.
You can do it.
It's just a case
of going out there
and start working on the street.
We hide a lot of stuff
in the church
and there is a lot of
bondage in the church,
but we need to get out there
and be doing it, on the edge.
God is real and He called us to
be His disciples, Jesus' disciples,
to go out and show
the world He is real.
This is real.
It is real. I tell you, it is real.
It's real!
It's really real!
It's really real, y'all!
This is real!
If this is real in the Bible,
what about the rest?
Every word is real,
from the beginning to the end.
Real.
This is real.
We are living in the last days,
where God is bringing His church
back to the truth,
back to the real life
we have been longing for.
The real life we have been
reading about in the Book of Acts,
where the Holy Spirit is leading.
This is happening, and it's
happening all over the world.
So let us keep the focus,
let us continue making disciples
and let Jesus build His church.
I believe it's
the last reformation
and this is just the beginning.
Do you still remember the word
I spoke to you?
Do you still remember the dream
I gave to you?
Time passes and the calendar's
filled up.
But one is necessary,
spend time with me.
Wake up, my people.
Soon, I'm coming back.
One is necessary.
Spend time with me.
I'm guiding you.
If you want to be my disciple,
you must deny yourself
and lay your own dreams down.
Follow me, no matter
what the cost is.
Then you will get eternal life.
Wake up, my people.
Soon, I'm coming back.
One is necessary.
Spend time with me.
I'm guiding you.
Do you have time for me?
To seek my Kingdom,
to seek my face.
I want to speak to you.
I want to lead you step by step.
I'm calling you.
Will you follow me
no matter what the cost is?
I'm calling you. I'm calling you.
Subtitles by: Mark Sheats, Robbert Dam,
Therese Visconti & Lourens Akkerman.